Finding Aid for the Anaïs Nin Papers, ca. 1910-1977 LSC.2066
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Diaries by Anaïs Nin, 1914-1965; 12.4 Linear Feet
  - Diaries by Anaïs Nin, 1939-1965; 9.0 lin ft. (106 folders)
    - Diary [82]. 1954 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[219]-[465]. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      AN's description of Inge Bogner, pp.[74]-[76] and comments throughout on her psychoanalysis with Bogner.
    - Diary [83]. 1954 - II. Hugo's letters, etc., pp.[1]-[187]. Looseleaf. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Hugh Guiler, Bill Seward, Maryat Lee, Clement Staff.
      With ephemera re "3 Films by Ian Hugo."
      Clippings and ephemera re various theatre productions.
    - Diary [83]. 1954 - II. Hugo's letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[188]-[397]. (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Hugh Guiler, Felix Pollak, Maryat Lee, Christmas card from Helen and Lloyd Wright, card from Eduardo [Sanchez].
      With ephemera for various dance and theatre productions.
      With horoscope for Gill Henderson, p.[293].
    - Diary [84]. 1955 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[225]. (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Rupert Pole, Lila Rosenblum, Alfred Perlès, Georges Borchardt, James Herlilhy, Ann Metzger, Felix Pollak, Renate [Druks], Kenneth Ness.
      Calendar pages for June, July, August, September throughout.
      With AN's notes on dreams and psychoanalysis with Inge Bogner. Mention of Caresse Crosby, p.[95].
    - Diary [84]. 1955 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[226]-[366]. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from Felix Pollak, James Herlihy, Margaret Crosland, Neville Armstrong, Mrs.Georges Simenon, p.[358], Hugh Guiler.
      With notes on dreams throughout.
      Notes re Lloyd Wright, pp.[334], [343]-[344].
    - Diary [85]. 1955 - [II]. Hugo letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[170]. (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Alfred Perlès, Eve Miller, James Herlihy, Anne Metzger, John Lehmann.
      AN's horoscope by Conrad Moricand, pp.[28]-[33].
      With printed material by Felix Anselm (Felix Pollak) and a poem, "A passing visit," p.[167].
    - Diary [85]. 1955 - [II]. Hugo letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[171]-[332]. (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Alfred Perles, James Herlihy, William Goyen, Rupert Pole, Sydney Omarr, Margaret Crosland, Joaquin Nin-Culmell.
      With theatre programs and ephemera.
      With AN's observations re dynamics of Christmas 1955 with Anne Baxter and the Lloyd Wright family, p.[331].
    - Diary [86]. 1956 - [I]. Mon Journal, 1956 January-June.; Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[107]. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from Romain Gary, Rupert Pole, Hugh Guiler, Felix Pollak, Neville Armstrong and others.
      With AN's letters to Rupert Pole and her notes on dreams and sessions with Inge Bogner.
      With AN's description of her diary (draft letter to prospective publishers) and lists of people who appear in the diary.
    - Diary [86]. 1956 - [I]. Mon Journal. Trip to Mexico. Sierra Madre. Work on Diary Copying 68. Work on Solar Bark [sic], 1956 July-December.; Looseleaf. pp.[108]-[317]. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from Neville Armstrong, Romain Gary, Rupert Pole, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Hugh Guiler, Tom Harshman and others.
      Program for Taliesen West concert.
      With letters from James Herlihy regarding the "black children" (diaries), pp.[133], [140] and production of his play Blue Denim as well as doing film work for David O. Selznick, pp.[218]-[219].
      With AN's observations on Reginald [Pole], p.[134].
    - Diary [87]. 1956 - [II]. Hugo letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[93]. (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Isabelle and Merle Armitage, Anne Metzger, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, James Herlihy and others.
      With program for June Wayne exhibit, San Francisco, p.[60].
    - Diary [87]. 1956 - [II]. Hugo letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[94]-[227]. (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Felix Pollak, Eve Miller, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, James Herlihy and others.
      With an undated letter from Allan Ginsberg which mentions "Isherwood & Jimmy Dean."
    - Diary [88]. 1957 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[185]. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Includes letters from Joaquin Nin-Culmell, William Watt, Hugh Guiler, Louis and Bebe Barron and others.
      With AN's observations on dreams, psychoanalysis with Bogner, Lloyd Wright, Rupert Pole, pp.[31]-[49].
      With paperback cover of A Spy in the House of Love.
      With AN's comments on Gore Vidal, pp.[52]-[55], Caresse Crosby p.[136].
    - Diary [88]. 1957 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[186]-[303]. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Lesley Blanch Gary, Hugh Guiler, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, James Herlihy, Anne Metzger and others.
      With AN's observations on failed relationships, Gore Vidal, life with Rupert, Helen and Lloyd Wright, Reginald Pole, pp.[259]-[[275] and her comments on her psychoanalysis with Inge Bogner.
    - Diary [88]. 1957 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[304]-[447]. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Includes letters from Marguerite Rebois, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Hugh Guiler and others.
      With copies of AN's letters to Lawrence Lipton, Larry & Claude Durrell, Lawrence Clark Powell.
      With photo of Rene Chochor, p.[417].
      AN's writings include her observations on returning to Rupert Pole, Helen and Lloyd Wright, the Malibu fire and Lloyd's anger towards RP, Lawrence Lipton, Henry Miller and June Miller.
      With her article, "Watts Towers - Simon Rodia," pp.[382a]-[389b].
    - Diary [89]. 1957 - [II]. Hugo letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[184]. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from Felix Pollak, Hugh Guiler, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, William Watt, Neville Armstrong, Eve Miller, James Herlihy, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Lawrence Durrell, Wallace Fowlie, Beatriz Guido, Gunther Stuhlman.
      With theatre programs, a program for a performance by Ravi Shankar and an article on seratonin.
    - Diary [90]. 1958 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[221]. (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from Rupert Pole, Hugh Guiler, Felix Pollak, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Gore Vidal, Lawrence Lipton, "Gil" and others.
      Includes correspondence between AN and Rupert Pole.
      With clippings and ephemera.
      With AN's observations on her dreams, sessions with Inge Bogner, Louis & Bebe Barron, Peggy Glanville Hicks, and trips to Paris and Brussels.
    - Diary [90]. 1958 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[222]-[429]. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Gunther Stuhlmann, Jean Varda, Eve Miller, "Guy," "Gil,"and others.
      With correspondence between AN and Rupert Pole. AN has written out some recipes, pp.[304]-[307].
    - Diary [90]. 1958 - [I], Looseleaf. pp.[430]-[529]. (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from Rupert Pole, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Lawrence Durrell, a postcard from Gore Vidal.
      With a carbon of AN's letter to GV, pp.[506]-[507] and her letters to Rupert Pole.
      With a letter from Eve Miller (6 November) re a visit from Henry Miller's daughter, Barbara, pp.[495]-[496].
    - Diary [91]. 1958 - [II], Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[149]. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Includes letters from "Marguerite," Maxwell Geismar, Caresse Crosby, pp.[43]-[44], [112], Lawrence Durrell, Gunther Stuhlmann, Tom Payne, Hans Richter, Lawrence Clark Powell, Hugh Guiler, Stanley Mills Haggart.
      With letters from James Herlihy, Margaret Crosland, Jane Morrison, Eve Miller, Mark Paterson, Eduardo Sanchez, Renate [Druks] and others.
    - Diary [91]. 1958 - [II], Looseleaf. pp.[150]-[314]. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Neville Armstrong, Maxwell Geismar, Peter Gwen, Mark Paterson, Marguerite[Rebois?], Gunther Stuhlmann, "Guy," "Olympia," and others.
    - Diary [92]. 1958 - [I], Hugo letters, etc, Looseleaf. pp.[151]-[314]. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from Felix Pollak, Hugh Guiler, Stanley Mills Haggart.
      With theatre programs, articles re the Grolier Book Shop in Cambridge, articles on new literary and artistic movements.
    - Diary [93]. Hugo letters, etc. II, 1958.; Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[158]. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from Gore Vidal, Felix [Pollak], Stanley Mills Haggart, Betty Eisner, Hugh Guiler, Jean Fanchette, Adele Comandini and others.
      With brochures re Harry Partch, clippings and theatre programs.
    - Diary [94]. 1959. 1x., Looseleaf. pp.[1[-[190]. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Daisy Aldan, Peter Gwen, Karl Shapiro, Jean Fanchette, Claude Durrell, James Herlihy, Gunther Stuhlmann, Eve Miller, Wallace Fowlie, Lawrence Durrell, Walter Wanger.
      Also includes letters from Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Hugh Guiler, Rupert Pole, Donald Greene, "Olympia," "Gil," and others.
      With "The Beats," by AN, pp.[73]-[76].
      (folder 1 of 4)
    - Diary [94]. 1959. 1x. The Fallen Jet., March 5, 1959.; "Blocgold" notebook with loose pages laid in. pp.[191]-[254]. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      With carbons of AN's letters to various people, including Max [Geismar] and Jean [Fanchette].
      Includes "The Fallen Jet" by AN, pp.[191]-[198], 5 March 1959.
      (folder 2 of 4)
    - Diary [94]. 1959. 1x. Capillary Bed., March 1959.; In "Blocgold" notebook. pp.[255]-299. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      With carbons of AN's letters to various people, including Caresse [Crosby], Peter Gwen, Lawrence Durrell, Daisy Aldan.
      (folder 3 of 4)
    - Diary [94]. 1959. 1x., Looseleaf. pp.[300]-[501]. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Daisy Aldan, James Herlihy, Jean Fanchette, Louise Varèse, Lawrence Durrell, Rupert Pole, Hugh Guiler, Eve Miller, Joaquin Nin-Culmell.
      With letters from Karl Shapiro, Henry Miller, Gunther Stuhlman, "Fran," "Lotte" and others.
      (folder 4 of 4)
    - Diary [95]. "106 [sic] May 1959 original.", Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[171]. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Jean Fanchette, Daisy Aldan, Paul Chase, Hugh Guiler, Rupert Pole, Gunther Stuhlmann, "Bella," Hans Richter, Hugo Raes, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Lawrence Durrell,"Marguerite" and others.
      Includes "Antonin Artaud" by AN, numbered pp.[57]-[61] and "Dream" by AN, numbered pp.[62]-[110].
    - Diary [95]. "106 [sic] May 1959 original.", Looseleaf. pp.[172]-[352]. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Jean Fanchette, Renate Druks, Hugh Guiler, Rupert Pole, Gunther Stuhlmann, Wallace Fowlie, Maxwell Geismar, Henry Miller, Karl Shapiro and others.
      With AN's letters to Rupert Pole, Joaquin Nin-Culmell.
      With "Three Black Dreams" and AN's reflections on New Year's Eve, [346]-[351].
      This folder includes photos of 1607-1/2 Silver Lake Blvd.
    - Diary [96]. 1959 I & II. Hugo's letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[153]. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Felix Pollak, an enclosure card from Gore Vidal, photos of Will Rogers Beach, letters from Stanley Mills Haggart, Gab Costalas and others.
      With disc recordings from Ian Hugo [Hugh Guiler] from Venice, Paris, Milan and photos of AN and Hugh Guiler in Venice (one negative available).
      With theatre programs and clippings.
    - Diary [97]. 1960 I all, Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[126]. (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, R.E. Blassick, Henry Miller, Rupert Pole, Roger Bloom, the Harvard Advocate.
      With theatre programs.
      With a copy of AN's letter to Walter Starke, p.[69].
    - Diary [97]. 1960 I all, Looseleaf. pp.[127]-[321]. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Includes letters from Rupert Pole, Roger Bloom, R.E. Blassick, Ronnie and Renate [Druks], Ruth Witt Diamant and others.
      With "The Minotaur" by Stanley Kurnick, p.[207] "To Anaïs Nin."
    - Diary [97]. 1960 I all, Looseleaf. pp.[322]-[471]. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Marguerite Young, R.E. Blassick, Rupert Pole, Daisy Aldan, Roger Bloom.
      Includes AN's letter to Yanko [Jean Varda] which describes the house in Silverlake designed for AN and Rupert Pole by Eric Wright.
    - Diary [98]. 1960 I. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[137]. (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, James Herlihy, Felix Pollak, Barbara Taylor, Lili Shepley, Daisy Aldan, Artur Lundkvist [?], Gunther Stuhlmann, Kathleen [Chase], Jean Fanchette and others.
    - Diary [98]. 1960 I. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[138]-[243]. (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, James Herlihy, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Felix Pollak, Daisy Aldan, Renate Druks, "Ottone" and others.
      With AN's letters to Roger Bloom.
    - Diary [98]. 1960 I. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[244]-[397]. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, James Herlihy, Gunther Stuhlmann, Stanley Mills Haggart, Gerald Malanga, Vincent Capanzano, Gregory Markopoulos, Phoenix Bookshop, Daisy Aldan and others.
    - Diary [99]. 1961. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[181]. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Includes a calendar for 1961, letters from Daisy Aldan, Roger Bloom, Hugh Guiler, James Herlihy, Lila Rosenblum, R.E. Blassick, Walter J. Carroll, Felix Pollak, Gilbert Neiman, William Watt, Harold Norse and others.
      With AN's letters to Roger Bloom. Theatre programs.
    - Diary [99]. 1961. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[182]-[345]. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Includes letters from Daisy Aldan, Roger Bloom, Hugh Guiler, Lila Rosenblum, R.E. Blassick, Walter J. Carroll, Robert Baldock, Alan Swallow, George Dibbern, "Ottone."
      With copies of AN's letters to Roger Bloom.
      With a copy of Hugh Guiler's (Ian Hugo's) letter to Harry Partch, p.[199].
    - Diary [100]. 1961. R-x, Looseleaf. pp.[1a]-[106]. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Includes folder labeled "Letter to Frances Keene, replace in "61."
      With letters from Alan Swallow, Jean Varda, Rupert Pole, Lila Rosenblum, Caresse Crosby, p.[31], Daisy Aldan, Louis & Bebe Barron.
      Also includes letters from Karl Shapiro, James Herlihy, Peter Own, Gilbert Neiman and others.
      With AN's letter written on behalf of Roger Bloom.
      With "Timothy Leary" by AN, pp.[14]-[24] and "Sinfonia Erotica " by AN, pp.[76]-[84].
    - Diary [100]. 1961. R-x, Looseleaf. pp.[107]-[203]. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Includes letters from Alan Swallow, Lila Rosenblum, Igrid Thulin Schein, Gunther Stuhlmann, Yanko [Jean Varda] and others.
      With AN's letters to Rupert Pole, Hugh Guiler, Joaquin Nin-Culmell.
    - Diary [100]. 1961. R-x (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Item numbered 204. "Leary and Alpert" by AN, written in a Japanese fanfold book, June 1961.
    - Diary [101]. 1961. R H letters, Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[203] (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Roger Bloom, Daisy Aldan, Karl Shapiro, Hugh Guiler, Lila [Rosenblum], Eve [Miller], R.E. Blassick, Harriet Zinnes, Robert Baldock, Felix Pollak, note from Gore Vidal, p.[144].
    - Diary [102]. 1961 all I, Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[92]. (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from Alan Swallow, Rupert Pole, Gilbert Neiman, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Larry Walrich, Phoenix Book Shop and others.
      With AN's letters to Hugh Guiler, Daisy Aldan, "Marguerite" and others.
    - Diary [102]. 1961 all I, Looseleaf. pp.[93]-[182]. (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Rupert Pole, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Gilbert Neiman, Phoenix Book Shop, Gunther Stuhlmann and others.
      With AN's letters to Hugh Guiler, Roger Bloom, Lila Rosenbloom and others.
    - Diary [102]. 1961 all I, Looseleaf. pp.[183]-[318]. (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from Alan Swallow, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Rupert Pole, James Herlihy, Maxwell Geismar, R.E. Blassick, Inge Bogner, Jean Varda, Jean Fanchette, Beatriz Guido, Eduardo Sanchez and others.
      Includes AN's letters to Rupert Pole, Roger Bloom, Daisy Aldan, Lila Rosenblum, Hugh Guiler, R.E. Blassick and others.
      This folder includes "The Final Reverie" by James Herlihy, typescript(carbon), pp.[238]-[243].
    - Diary [103]. 1962. R., January-April 1962.; Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[122]. (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Includes letters from Felix [Pollak], Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Henry Miller (photocopies), Oliver Evans, James Herlihy, Arthur Larents, Jerry Bick and others.
      With AN's letters to Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Roger Bloom, Hugh Guiler, and others.
    - Diary [103]. 1962. R., January-April 1962.; Looseleaf. pp.[123]-[248]. (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Oliver Evans, George Dibbern, Rupert Pole, Karl Shapiro, Gunther Stuhlmann, Caresse Crosby, pp.[201]-[202], Glenway Wescott, pp.[216]-[218], Tracey Roberts, Daisy Aldanand others.
      With "Raven Arrives on Flight 11" by AN, pp.[123]-[128] and a copy of [AN's?] review of the film La Notte by Antonioni, p.[129].
      With AN's letters to Rupert Pole, Felix Pollak, Alan Swallow and others.
    - Diary [104]. 1962. R x., May-December 1962.; Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[115]. (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Includes letters from Roger Shattuck, Alan Swallow, Hugh Guiler, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Gunther Stuhlmann, George Wickes, Lawrence Durrell, Henry Miller.
      Also includes letters from Joaquin Nin-Culmell, R.E. Blassick, Oliver Evans, Daisy Aldan, Rupert Pole, Maxwell Geismar and others.
      With AN's letters to Rupert Pole, Hugh Guiler, Alan Swallow, Robert Baldock and others.
      With letters from Wilbur Smith re AN's request for an exchange of Henry Miller/AN letters.
    - Diary [104]. 1962. R x., May-December 1962.; pp.[116]-[261]. Looseleaf. (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Includes letters from Alan Swallow, Hugh Guiler, Robert Baldock, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Gunther Stuhlmann, George Wickes, Anne Metzger.
      With letters from Lawrence Durrell, Henry Miller (some photocopies), Rupert Pole, Oliver Evans, Bill Routt and others.
      With letters from Wilbur Jordan Smith and Brooke Whiting, UCLA Library, regarding an exchange of Henry Miller/AN letters.
      Includes a description of her "griefs against Henry [Miller], 8 Aug.," pp.[234]-[247] and further comments on Henry Miller, pp.[248]-[253].
    - Diary [105]. 1962. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[154]. (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from James Herlihy, Hugh Guiler, Roger Bloom, Daisy Aldan, Kathleen Chase and others.
      Calendar pages interspersed.
    - Diary [105]. 1962. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[155]-[348]. (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Roger Bloom, Daisy Aldan, Eduardo [Sanchez] and others.
      With calendar pages interspersed, as well as film programs, and fan letters.
    - Diary [105]. 1962. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[349]-[516]. With calendar pages interspersed. (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Gunther Stuhlmann, Roger Bloom, Andre Bay and others.
    - Diary [105]. 1962. H letters, etc., Looseleaf. pp.[517]-[643]. (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Roger Bloom, Anne Metzger, "Carol," "Lynne," "Marguerite" and others.
      With AN's letters to Roger Bloom, Hugh Guiler and others.
      With calendar pages, fan letters and film programs interspersed.
    - Diary [106]. 1963, R × all, January-May 1963.; Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[39]. (Box 34, Folder 5)
      "Journal des Autres, 1963."
    - Diary [106]. 1963, R × all, January-May 1963.; Looseleaf. pp.[40]-[151]. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Alan Swallow, Gerald Robitaille, Andre Bay, Henry Miller (photocopies), Nobuko Uenishi, Oliver Evans, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Harry T. Moore, Fernand Ouellette, Gunther Stuhlmann and others.
      With copies of AN's letters to Hugh Guiler, Rupert Pole, Inge Bogner and others.
      With a copy of AN's letter to Lloyd Wright, p.[144].
    - Diary [106]. 1963, R × all, January-May 1963.; Looseleaf. pp.[152]-[278]. (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Includes letters from Alan Swallow, Andre Bay, Henry Miller (photocopies), Adelle Davis, Nobuko Uenishi, Oliver Evans, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Gunther Stuhlmann, Jascha Kessler, Rupert Pole.
      With letters from Gilbert Neiman, Stanley Berre, Jerry Bick and others.
      With AN's assessments of Tennessee Williams, Truman Capote, Glenway Wescott, pp.[186]-[189].
    - Diary [106]. 1963, R × all, January-May 1963.; Looseleaf. pp.[279]-[409]. (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Includes letters from Alan Swallow, Andre Bay, Henry Miller (photocopies), Nobuko Uenishi, Oliver Evans, Wallace [Fowlie?], Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Lawrence and Claude Durrell, Yanko [Jean Varda], Daisy Aldan.
      With letters from Marguerite Duras, Harry T. Moore, Renate Gerhardt, Gunther Stuhlmann, Anne Metzger, Pierre Brodin, Jerry Bick, Karl Shapiro, Peter Gwen, Renate [Druks?] and others.
      With AN's letters to Hugh Guiler, Gunther Stuhlman, Daisy Aldan and others.
    - Diary [107]. 1963 II - all, H letters, etc., R, Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[199]. (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Roger Bloom, Daisy Aldan, Pierre Brodin and others.
      With issue of "IFIF [International Federation for International Freedom] Newsletter," clippings.
    - Diary [107]. 1963 II - all, H letters, etc., R, Looseleaf. pp.[200]-[432]. With clippings. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Marguerite [Young], Roger Bloom, Daisy Aldan, Pierre Brodin, Harry T. Moore, Bruce Tsuchida, Anne Metzger, Esther Longtree, offices of L'Herne.
    - Diary [108]. 1964 - all. Mon Journal. Journal des Autres, Looseleaf. pp.[1]-[202]. (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Daisy Aldan, Alan Swallow, Gunther Stuhlmann, "Marguerite,"Karl Shapiro, Andre Bay, Tracey [Roberts].
      With letters from Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Jerry Bick, Nobuko Uenishi, Harry T. Moore, Henry Miller (photocopies), Bruce Tsuchida, Daisy Aldan, Oliver Evans and others.
      With AN's letters to Hugh Guiler, Alan Swallow, Rupert Pole and others.
      With clippings on Frank Stella and Jasper Johns.
      (folder 1 of 5)
    - Diary [108]. 1964 - all. Mon Journal. Journal des Autres, Looseleaf. pp.[203]-[379]. (Box 35, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from Rupert Pole, Daisy Aldan, Hugh Guiler, Alan Swallow, Gunther Stuhlmann, Marguerite Duras, Lawrence & Claude Durrell, Arthur Laurents, Andre Bay, Eduardo Sanchez, Tracey Roberts, Oliver Evans.
      With letters from Nona Balakian, Bruce Tsuchida, Harry T. Moore, Kathleen Chase, Jean Vardaand others.
      With copies of AN's Letters to Rupert Pole, Hugh Guiler.
      (folder 2 of 5)
    - Diary [108]. 1964 - all. Mon Journal. Journal des Autres, Looseleaf. pp.[380]-[514]. (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Includes letters from Daisy Aldan, Hugh Guiler, Roger Bloom, Oliver Evans, Joseph Losey, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Nona Balakian, Peter Gwen, Nobuko Uenishi.
      With letters from Hugo Raes, Bill Routt, Marguerite Duras, Henry Miller (photocopies), Jerry Bick, Anne Metzger and others.
      With copies of AN's letters to Gunther Stuhlmann, Hugh Guiler, Rupert Pole and others.
      (folder 3 of 5)
    - Diary [108]. 1964 - all. Mon Journal. Journal des Autres, Looseleaf. pp.[515]-[650]. (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from Bruce Tsuchida, Hugh Guiler, Alan Swallow, Jerry Bick, Harry T. Moore, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Roger Bloom, Gunther Stuhlmann.
      With letters from Daisy Aldan, Marguerite Duras, Andre Bay, Oliver Evans, Jean Varda, Joseph Losey and others.
      With AN's letters to Bruce Tsuchida, Hugh Guiler, Daisy Aldan, Gunther Stuhlmann and others.
      (folder 4 of 5)
    - Diary [108]. 1964 - all. Mon Journal. Journal des Autres, Looseleaf. pp.[651]-[825]. (Box 35, Folder 7)
      Includes letters from Hugh Guiler, Nona Balakian, Alan Swallow, Anne Metzger, Jerry Bick, Joaquin Nin-Culmell, Oliver Evans, Jean Varda, Joseph Losey, Ray Bradbury, Daisy Aldan, Henry Miller (photocopies) and others.